[Music]
Success is a journey,
not a destination, for Mr. Nguyen Manh
Luong, Assistant Senior Vice President of
Agency System at Manula Vietnam. It
's a journey of passion,
relentless effort, and unwavering dedication to
his chosen work. The humanistic philosophy
of the life insurance industry, along with the
professional working environment at
Manula, is the driving force behind his commitment and
success over the past 15 years.
I have a
strong sense of humanity and compassion, which is reflected in
two things: the financial values
that customers invest and save in a
disciplined manner to have a
comfortable life, or at least to
have financial plans for
their children. If the family faces
any risks in life,
those financial resources can
help the wife, husband,
parents, or children continue
to have a good financial foundation. Before
joining online insurance, I was the
director of a company in Hong Kong.  In
Ho Chi Minh City, I attended a
career development event at Menol and saw
that Menol is a
very professional financial, insurance, and investment group
with a
strong track record of growth over the past 115 years.
After nearly two years working as a
financial consultant, I was
promoted from
deputy head of department to Business Director. After many years,
I had the opportunity to be assigned by the company
to work and build many
offices in provinces and cities nationwide.
Currently, I manage
2500 financial consultants. There are
three factors that I am most impressed with. The
first is the leadership
structure; Menol's leadership team is currently
very good, especially the
key leadership. The second factor,
which I think is equally important,
is the company's strategies and direction,
which are very
clear. And the last factor, which I think has
also contributed to my success to
date, is...  Those are the
cultural norms, a tradition
of training, supervision,
and management—almost daily tasks that provide
guidance to
sales managers in various regions and
provinces, ensuring they follow
the company's strategies set at the
beginning of the year. My experience
is based on a 5P formula: the
first P stands for "
professional"—working
professionally; the second P stands for "passion,"
meaning employees must have a passion
for their
work; the third P stands for "performance," meaning
they must have
activities that lead to achievements; the
fourth P stands for "PR," meaning they must be proud of
the organization they work for; and the
final P, which I particularly appreciate,
is "persistence," meaning they
must have a sense of commitment.
What I've felt and appreciated
most is the
genuine affection shared by all the
financial advisors I've
worked with.  Having shared and
accompanied me for the past 15 years,
we have a belief that there is still
an opportunity to contribute and
continue to develop at K min la for
many years to come.
[music]
m [
music]